And are south sides of the far story
And to say that in ways I could
Because so much made me not matter to me
It's still the inch, I'll probably always be
Asteroids, most people never see
Impossible questions filled
No stars and symbols, that's always been me
But one thing was never strange
The way I looked at you, that part was always real
Turning every scribe, fucking Steve, was released without charges.
You know, nobody, nobody like, really like, even Paige, I thought Paige would be like,
psych, I love you. I mean, she always was like, I don't like that, but she's like, oh yeah,
you were kind of like, one of the people that I met first. It's probably more Vita.
You know, Vita was, Vita was cool. I like Vita. She's like the Phoenix of Rises.
And you're just a piece of shit. Sorry. Anyway, I don't know. I'll be back.
Ladies and gentlemen, trolls and troublemakers, moderators and lurkers, step right up!
Welcome to the greatest criminal enterprise, I actually committed a crime.
Camcrowd folding share throw, a tarot reed dreamed, in profit full time controller, there was
and treasured deep but it was 47 ring lights and merchandise we'd never keep
one shit tarot card, one ship stickers, one sold cursed mugs to internet snickers
one delivered noodles across state lines, the trolls get agonized,
CROCK!
8 months investigating, chat recaps, another claim he had
What's tonight's shipment?
3 tarot decks, 2 pizzas, a rubber duck, like and subscribe
The package, a burrito, the mule, a guy named Steve who lost his GPS Reno. Federal agents arrived, the trolls all cheered, the evidence, locker contained, 37 mugs and novelty hats, a crystal ball and a cat, the cat.
Mother show, and somewhere in the darkness, a moderator whispered, guys, the ramen shipmen arrived.
It's a black and mirror
Be with the hallway, trying ghosts of old dope
Yeah, you remember the ones I used to leave cracked
But I'm the one with the ring of iron keys and I don't bow
Yeah, keep your lips back, cause you can take it
You love the ache of it
Baby, I'ma spin you, I'll play you like a slow song
The pages tell me where I swore anything's sacred
I never caught promises and stoned
I caught warnings and developed
You're thirst, I'm the stone, and we both know why
Oh, I got waves and you clean cuz you can take and you mistake it for devotion
Baby, I'ma spin your skin till the needle's tired and play you I'll keep you turning like a slow song
Like a slow song till the groove can't run
You like a slow song. I'll play you like a slow song
Talking like you're a fool
I count a print for the job
Sit down though
You call your man this whole